Let's start with a discussion of distributions.
讓我們從討論分佈(distribution)開始吧。
And we'll start with the most common using a coin.
我們從最常用的硬幣測試開始。
When a coin is flipped it has a probability of landing heads up and
當一個硬幣翻轉時，它有一個落的頭部向上的可能性，和
a probability of landing tails up.
一個落的尾巴向上的可能性。
If we flip a coin many times we collect a number of measurements of the heads and
如果我們翻轉硬幣多次，我們會收集一些數據，頭部和
tails that landed face up and
尾巴向上的次數，
intuitively we know that the number of times we get a heads up
直覺地，我們知道我們得到頭部的次數
will be equal about the number of times we get a tails up for a fair coin.
將相當於我們得到尾巴的次數，用一個公平的硬幣。
If you flipped a coin a hundred times and
如果你翻了硬幣一百次，
you received heads each time you'd probably doubt the fairness of that coin.
你每次都得到頭部，你可能會懷疑這枚硬幣的公平性。
We can consider the result of each flip of this coin as a random variable.
我們可以將這個硬幣的每次翻轉的結果作為隨機(random)變數來考慮。
When we can consider the set of all possible random variables together
當我們可以一起考慮所有可能的隨機變數的集合時，
we call this a distribution.
我們稱之為一個分佈(distribution)。
In this case the distribution is called binomial
在這種情況下，分佈被稱為二項式(binomial)，
since there's two possible outputs a heads or a tails.
因為有兩個可能的輸出，頭或尾。
It's also an example of a discreet distribution since there are only
這也是一個離散值(discreet)分佈的例子，因為只有
categories being used a heads and a tails and not real numbers.
使用類別(category)，頭和尾，而不是實數。
NumPy actually has some distributions built into it
Numpy 實際上有一些內建的分佈
allowing us to make random flips of a coin with given parameters.
讓我們可以隨機翻轉硬幣，用給定的參數。
Let's give it a try.
讓我們試試看吧。
Here we ask for a number from the NumPy binomial distribution.
這裡我們從NumPy二項式(binomial)分佈中計算一個數字
We have two parameters to pass in.
我們有兩個參數要傳入：
The first is the number of times we want it to run.
第一個是我們希望運行的次數。
The second is the chance we get a zero, which we will use to represent heads here.
第二個是我們得到零的機會， 我們這裡將使用它來代表頭
Let's run one round of this simulation.
我們來運行一輪這個模擬。
Great so
太好了，
if you're following along in a Jupyter notebook you either got a zero or a one.
所以如果你在Jupyter筆記本上跟著， 你可能會得到一個0或1
And half of you got a value that agreed with the one that I got.
一半的人得到了一個與我所得到的值一樣的值。
What if we run the simulation a thousand times and
如果我們運行模擬一千次，
divided the result by a thousand.
將結果除以一千？
Well you see a number pretty close to 0.5 which
那麼你看到的數字很接近0.5，這
means half of the time we had a heads and half of the time we had a tails.
意味著我們有一半的時間我們有一個頭， 有一半的時間，我們有一個尾巴。
Of course an even weighted binomial distribution is only one simple example.
當然，均勻加權(even weighted)二項式分佈只是一個簡單的例子。
We can also have unevenly weighted binomial distributions.
我們也可以具有不均勻加權的二項式分佈。
For instance what's the chance although we're tornado today while I’m filming.
例如，當我今天在拍攝時，有龍捲風的機會是什麼
It's pretty low even though we do get tornadoes here.
即使我們這裡有龍捲風，機率也很低
So maybe there a hundredth of a percentage chance.
也許有百分之幾的機率
We can put this into a binomial distribution as a weighting in NumPy.
我們可以把它放進二項式分佈的加權值在NumPy中
If we run this 100,000 times we see there are pretty minimal tornado events.
如果我們跑10萬次，我們看到有非常少的龍捲風事件。
So you might be wondering why I'm talking about such a simple and
你可能會想知道為什麼我說這麼簡單和
intuitive distribution.
直觀的分佈。
I mean we all understand flipping a coin for
我的意思是說，我們都明白翻轉硬幣，
when we had to make important decisions as children.
作為孩子，當我們不得不做出重要決定的時候 。
But what I want to demonstrate is that the computational tools are starting to allow
但是我想顯示的是，計算工具開始允許
us to simulate the world which helps us answer questions.
我們模擬世界的現象，有助於我們回答問題。
I could have shown you the math behind this so
我可以告訴你們這個背後的數學，
we could have worked out the probabilities.
我們可以計算出概率。
But a simulation is essentially another form of inquiry.
但是模擬本質上是另一種形式的查詢。
Let's take one more example.
我們再來一個例子。
Let's say the chance of a tornado here in Ann Arbor on any given day,
讓我們說，龍捲風在Ann Arbor發生的機會，在任何一天
is 1% regardless of the time of year.
是1％，不管一年中任何的時間
That's higher than realistic but it makes for a quicker demo.
這比現實的高，但更快的演示。
And lets say if there's a tornado I'm going to get away from the windows and
讓我們說，如果有一個龍捲風，我要遠離窗戶並
hide, then come back and do my recording the next day.
躲避，然後第二天再回來做錄音
So what's the chance of this happening two days in a row?
那麼連續兩天發生龍捲風的機率是甚麼？
Well we can use the binomial distribution in NumPy to simulate this.
那麼我們可以使用NumPy中的二項式分佈來模擬這個
Here we create an empty list and we create a number of potential tornado events by
這裡我們創建一個空列表，我們創建一些潛在的龍捲風事件，通過
asking the NumPy binomial function using our chance of tornado.
問NumPy二項式函數，和使用我們龍捲風的機率
We'll do this a million times which is just shy of 3,000 years worth of events.
我們會做這一百萬次，這只是稍微少於3000年的事件。
This process is called sampling the distribution.
這個過程稱為分佈採樣(sampling)。
Now we can write a little loop to go through the list and look for
現在我們可以寫一個循環(loop)來經歷列表，找出
any two adjacent pairs of ones which means
兩個相鄰的一對1，這意味著
that there were two days that had back to back tornadoes.
持續兩天有龍捲風
We see that this ends up being roughly 102 day tornado events over the 3,000 years.
我們看到，最終大概有102天的龍捲風事件(持續兩天)，在這3000年的時間里。
Which frankly is still too many for me.
坦白說，對我來說還是太多了。
My point here though is that modern computational power allows us to very
我的觀點是，現代計算能力使我們能夠非常
quickly simulate the effects of different parameters in a distribution.
快速地模擬，不同的參數對分佈的影響。
Leading to a new way of understanding the problem.
導致一種新的理解問題的方式。
You don't have to work out all the math you can
你不必解決所有的數學問題，你可以
quite often simulate the problem instead and observe the results.
很經常模擬問題，並觀察結果。
In the next lecture we'll talk a little bit more about distributions.
在接下來的講課中，我們將再談一下分佈。